{
    "id": "cbd47791bc904e6fb441ea731b005fe9",
    "title": "For, In, From, and Since | Grammar Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "6749b786c64042a49e023e627eed349d",
            "title": "For, In, From, and Since | Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I once studied the violin .......................... six months.",
                    "description": "Use for with periods of time. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have known him ........................... our school days.",
                    "description": "Since gives the starting point of an action or situation. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "That house has been empty ......................... several years.",
                    "description": "Use for with a period of time. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "from",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long have you been here ...........................?",
                    "description": "For shows duration. Use it with a period of time. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has not been keeping good health ........................... he moved to the city.",
                    "description": "Since gives the starting point of something. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am going to my native place ........................... the summer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They are getting married ............................. July.",
                    "description": "Use in before the names of months and seasons. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "since",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................ now on, I am going to go jogging every day.",
                    "description": "From gives the starting point of an action or situation. We mainly use it with simple tenses. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "From",
                        "Since",
                        "For"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The shop was open .......................... six in the morning.",
                    "description": "From is mainly used with simple tenses. Since is mainly used with perfect tenses. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "since",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Trees shed their leaves ................................. autumn.",
                    "description": "Use in before the names of months and seasons. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "for",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have been working .................................. 10 o'clock and I am getting tired.",
                    "description": "We mainly use since with perfect and perfect continuous tenses. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "since",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have known her ......................... Monday.",
                    "description": "Use since with the starting point. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "since",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}